My name is Ms Rebecca.
I'm from Ghana.
I have needles in my body and have been operated on several times.
I am still not okay.
The doctors have removed 18 needles but I am still not okay.
That is the reason why I'm here.
I know through Christ I am going to be healed.
Where are those needles in your body?
These are the scars.
They operated on you?
Yes.
Let's see.
These are the places where they removed the needles?
Yes, these are the places where the needles were removed from.
But each place where they removed the needles - what happened to the place?
In the same place, they would still find needles, up to five.
Inside the same spot?
Yes.
Immediately they stitched it?
So how many needles have they removed?
About eighteen.
Can we see the needles that they removed.
These are some of the needles.
And they have removed how many of these?
Eighteen.
Eighteen?
Yes.
Can you tell us how many needles are in your body now.
I can't tell how many are left.
Let's see the X-ray.
This is the X-ray.
You can see those lines - they are the needles.
This is where they removed the needles from.
Why did they stop removing them?
The spot where they removed needles, five would enter.
Is that the reason why they stopped?
Yes.
They stopped removing the needles because at each spot where they removed needles,
by the time they stitched it, five would enter.
Whenever they removed a needle from a particular place,
the following week, when I went for an X-ray, they would find 5 more needles.
In the same spot?
Yes.
Can we see the medical report, the statement given to you from the doctor.
This is the medical report.
It is from a specialist from the Ghanuba Clinic, Accra.
The doctor asked me to bring it here because it was beyond his understanding.
So, the medical report here is from Ghanuba Clinic.
It is written, "To whom it may concern.
Dear sir or madam; a medical report concerning Rebecca Idi.
The above patient has been under my care since last year.
She reported with chronic abdominal pain.
Diagnosis of umbilical hernia was made for which she was operated.
About about one month, she reported with abdominal pain
and this time a swelling was noted above the umbilicus, in the midline.
This was interpreted as epigastric hernia and was again operated
and this time a needle was retrieved from the site.
She reported again with the same pain.
An X-ray conducted revealed multiple needles on the X-ray film.
So far I have surgically removed about twelve of the needles from the abdominal wall.
A follow-up X-ray still reveals the presence of such needles.
This is beyond my understanding.
Any help offered her is therefore highly appreciated.
Dr Twumasi, a Senior Surgeon at Ghanuba Clinic in Ghana.
There are now 1000 needles in the body.
How many have they removed?
They removed eighteen.
You have seen the spots where they removed them.
At each spot, one was removed and almost five entered back.
What do you want to say about this?
What I want to educate you about this is that
when you remove it physically, you double the problem.
Because it was commanded in by incantation - evil spirit,
it must also be commanded out by the Holy Spirit.
It is not something you are supposed to see with your naked eyes.
The people that are doing this do not carry the needles and throw them
or put it in the food or drink.
They command it, and it enters invisibly.
We are not fighting the flesh and blood.
The command is not by throwing it or giving food or poison.
If a situation has become a curse - this is a curse - who can remove the curse?
This is why He was crucified.
He died on the cross.
They command it in by the power of evil spirit
and we command that thing out in the name of Jesus Christ.
The thing was not commanded three times.
It was commanded once by the power of evil spirit and thousands entered.
It is not one at a time that they command.
Evil spirit, take it.
No.
The whole thing; thousands were commanded and thousands entered.
A just mere opening of our lips, calling the name of Jesus,
the whole thousand too will disappear.
Little girl, had you ever experienced this in the family?
Maybe needles are a generational curse in your family.
People have needles in their body when they are born.
Or does any person have needles in his body?
I am the only person having this problem in the family.
You see the way she talks.
Some of those needles are close to her heart.
It is just everywhere in her body.
You said you are the only person in the family?
Yes.
How did this thing enter your body?
I don't know how they got into my body.
The doctor gave me a magnet to be rubbing on my tummy
so that they could come up to the skin surface for them to cut.
Ok.
Each time the doctor wants to remove them,
he will give you a magnet?
Yes, I have the magnet in the house.
The magnet that magnetised the needles?
Yes.
You then used a magnet to rub your body?
Then, it would come up to the skin.
I would go to the hospital for them to cut and remove the needles.
My God.
She will meet me at the prayer line.
Man of God, please help me.
Because of this situation, I couldn't complete my education
and I am always at home, suffering all the time.
As you are standing now, can you point to where you suspect the needles?
From this side to my pelvis.
It is all right.
She said she can locate some here.
Man of God, please help me.
I don't want to go for surgery anymore.
If God sent me to this lady today, I will be the most delighted person here.
To see how this girl will be free.
Those needles in the body - just like that eventually.
The person who did that will be brought to book.
What other efforts did you make in trying to remove the needles in your body?
Through traditional healers.
Are you a Christian?
Yes, sir.
Give it to the sister.
My name is Ms Julia Kujah.
I brought her from Ghana.
Her father works for me.
She has been in and out of hospitals and had several surgeries done.
The more surgeries they did, the more needles they found.
Her father recently came to me and said someone introduced him to a traditional healer
and that he wanted to take her there.
I told him not to but he was desperate.
I couldn't stop him because that was his child.
Then, he went.
He told me that the traditional healer used an egg to rub her body.
The needles entered the egg; they broke it and took the needles out.
I told him that he was going to compound this girl's problems,
that it was spiritual, created by satan and only Jesus could save her.
He came back to me a few days later and said he had thought about what I had said.
I told him, "Persuade the doctor so he will be willing to give you a medical report.
Then, we will go to the arena of liberty; I know Jesus can heal her".
That is how far we have come.
Can you see the huge challenges we have now.
We have made the name Jesus unpopular.
Nobody believes again.
Before people can come to Jesus, it means there is nowhere else to go.
They might have gone far and spent a fortune.
I asked if she is a Christian.
She said she is a Christian.
But she never thought of going to a man of God.
Did you pray over this thing?
Yes, we have.
We have been to so many churches.
Yes, they have been to many churches for prayer and deliverance but to no avail.
There is no other way for medical doctors but to recommend surgery
and they would have to operate on the whole body.
As you operate and stitch, five will go back at the same spot.
It is a sign to tell us that there are powers that cause people to bow down.
My sister, don't worry.
God asked you to come here and I know the same God will deliver you.
Amen.
That is it.
Let us wait for God's time.
At God's time which I know will be now.
HEALING TIME
21-year-old Ms Rebecca Idi has come all the way from Ghana to The SCOAN
with an unusual problem of needles in her body.
She had been operated on several times where a total of 18 needles were removed.
This is the X-ray that shows the numerous needles that are still inside her body, despite the surgeries.
This is a medical report from a hospital in Ghana that attested to their inability
to provide a permanent solution, despite many treatments and surgeries.
Here are some of the needles that were removed by the doctors through surgery.
After these needles were removed through operation, the doctors did a follow-up X-ray
and to their surprise, it showed the presence of even more needles in her body.
The doctors were completely mystified by the case and made a decision to no longer take any action.
This problem has indeed gone beyond the power of nature, beyond medical science and technology.
It has become a curse.
Who can remove the curse?
Only Jesus Christ.
Prophet T.B. Joshua, under the influence of the Holy Spirit, has been used by Jesus Christ
to break every curse in the lives of the people.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ, every mountain, curse and chain is being removed
and they are restored back to the original position God Almighty created them.
Among those being prayed for at the prayer line is Ms Rebecca Idi,
with the problem of needles in her body.
Man of God, please help me.
My name is Ms Rebecca.
I am from Ghana.
I have needles in my body and they keep on pricking me all the time.
Please help me, Man of God.
Please help me.
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Man of God, please help me.
I have needles in my body and they keep on pricking me.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
You are free.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Lord, I am free!
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus, I am free!
Thank You, Lord, I am free!
It is not something you would not know.
She herself should know whether she is free.
It is not just issue of, "By faith, I am free".
Because the pain is there; she feels the pain, the needles, everything.
Take her somewhere and let her check herself.
Give her two to five minutes to check and then come back.
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
The thing came by evil spirit and we have to command it out by Holy Spirit.
This is a test to our faith.
If there is anything called miracle, this is a miracle.
This is what we call signs and wonders.
It is not an issue of headache going but you can see the needles brought out
and you can see thousand needles inside.
Signs and wonders.
The same way Moses said to the Red Sea.
Thank You, Lord!
Thank You, Jesus, for saving my life!
We are talking of the command Elijah used when the little children were calling him "bald head man"
and he commanded the bear to come out and eat them.
They could not even find the bones and blood on the floor.
We call it a command.
It is not an issue of, "In the name of Jesus, go. In the name of Jesus, I rebuke, I bind".
If that is what Daniel used in the lion den, the lion would have removed one hand
before Jesus comes to the rescue.
The way you offer prayer today, "In Jesus' name, I rebuke.
In Jesus' name, I bind".
The lion will not hear that; the lion will not wait for that.
Half of the body would have been gone before Jesus came to the rescue.
Three men, Meshach, Shadrach, and Abednego, at the furnace.
A fire that nothing can be compared with.
They were dropped inside.
Even before they landed, if they had prayed like, "In the name of Jesus, I rebuke, I stop the fire",
I think the fire would have consumed them before that time.
Try to understand the command.
There is command and there is a command.
Ms Rebecca Idi, set free by a command in the name of Jesus Christ,
goes to a nearby restroom to check her body.
God, thank You so much for healing me.
I am free.
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus, for healing me!
Praise the living God!
I cannot feel the needle pricks anymore.
Thank You, Jesus, for sаving my life.
I don't feel the needle pricks anymore.
They have disappeared!
I thank God so much.
Ms Rebecca Idi testifies that she can no longer feel the sharp pain
caused by the needles in her body.
Thank You, Lord, I am free!
I don't feel the needle pricks anymore.
Thank You, Jesus!
Come on.
Have you checked yourself?
Are you free?
Before when I would touch my tummy, I would feel the needle pricks.
I don't feel them anymore.
Let me tell you something that happened at the healing section.
I never knew when that would happen.
I was thinking that it would be today.
When I stood here and she was talking, I saw it and I was looking at it
but I never heard anything.
How would this thing be done?
I knew that with God all things are possible and I was looking at it.
But I never knew that the whole thing would happen that day.
So, when I was moving round at the prayer line, I didn't see any green light -
an indication that I should pray for her.
I was praying for everyone; I was just moving.
Before I got to her, Prophet T.B. Joshua had got there already.
This is the lady here.
Stand up!
Stand close to your seat there!
When I was with this man, the resurrection power had already got to the lady.
The footprint of God.
Do you know what I mean with the footprint of God?
It moves with our shadow.
When we move, it is mostly on our shadow.
Look at you - I am on you.
Can you see the shadow?
See the shadow.
That is shadow.
That is the shadow.
The shadow overwhelmed him.
That shadow that overwhelmed him is full of lightning.
It is not thunder.
It is more than thunder.
Thunder is an agent of God.
But when I say "lightning", I mean the resurrection power that can go beyond the wall.
When it lights through the wall, it comes out at the other side.
But thunder - no.
Can you see that it has still captured him.
He could not move.
The resurrection power.
The same resurrection power can put him on the floor.
Look at him.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
That's it.
That is it.
That is the resurrection power - how powerful!
It can move.
How powerful.
And not only him; He can bring all of them together and make them fall.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You may be seated.
When I was moving and the sister was there, before getting to the sister,
the Lord was telling me, "Don't be afraid. Go there", because I had already seen a sign.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
When I realised the presence of God was there before me,
I just had to grab the shoulder.
When I grabbed the shoulder, all the needles were right in my hand.
Right in my hand and it was needles I threw, not the lady.
The needles had made her become heavy.
When I pulled out the needles and they were in my hand, I just threw them away.
Because she was very light, she fell.
It was not her that was supposed to fall.
Let's see the sister.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Can you see the lady?
Can you put the former face to this face - needle face to God's face.
Let's hear from her.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ms Rebecca; I'm from Ghana.
Beside me are my dad, my mum, my elder brothers, my kid-sister and my kid-brother
and my auntie who helped me to come here.
In fact, you can look at me and compare me to my former appearance.
I was here last week Sunday.
I had needles in my body.
I had gone to so many places - so many doctors, herbal healers - but to no avail.
I was always in pain.
I was not schooling or doing anything.
I couldn't eat, walk or sleep.
A lady introduced me to The SCOAN.
She brought me here, last week.
I was placed on the prayer line, where the man of God prayed for me.
After he prayed for me, I examined myself very well.
I could not feel any pricks in my tummy.
I could eat, do everything, walk well, and sleep like a baby - no more pain.
I am so grateful to God for saving my life.
Rebecca
(Prayer Line Testimony)
After the prayer, I kept on asking myself each day,
"Where are the pins God removed from me?
They are nowhere to be found".
I thank God for saving me.
Now, I don't feel any pain anymore, anywhere.
I can do anything.
So, I thank God for what He has done for me, in Jesus' name.
Rebecca
(Prayer Line Testimony)
Little girl, now you keep wondering where the pins are?
Yes, I always wonder how.
I don't know where they are.
I am so excited.
After the prayer, you went to press those places where you felt the pain.
You knew the pain was there.
You could not feel those needles there again?
Not at all.
After the prayer, I examined myself.
I pressed my tummy.
I didn't feel the pricking that I used to feel whenever I pressed my tummy.
Your urine is clear now? There is nothing like blood?
Yes, everything is okay.
I am okay; I am alright - nothing.
Rebecca
(Prayer Line Testimony)
And you sleep very well now - no nightmares?
I now sleep like a newborn baby; I am okay!
I don't have sleepless nights anymore.
In the past, before you were prayed for, what were you experiencing every night?
In my dreams, I would see someone giving me food to eat.
But now, I don't have those kind of dreams anymore -
someone chasing me to kill me - I don't have them anymore.
Do you know the power you are under?
Sing this song along with me - Majesty.
Majesty
Worship His majesty
Unto Jesus
Be all glory, honour and praise
Majesty
Kingdom authority
Flows from His throne unto His own
His anthem raise
So exalt
Lift up on high
The name of Jesus
Magnify
Come glorify
Christ Jesus the King
Majesty
Worship His majesty
Jesus who died
Now glorified
King of all kings
Jesus who died
Now glorified
King of all kings
You may be seated; thank you.
Take your Bible and read the Book of John 3.
Start reading from verse 32.
The Book of John 3:32, "He testifies to what he has seen and heard".
He testifies to what he has seen and heard.
John 3:32, "but no one accepts his testimony".
No one accepts his testimony.
John 3:33, "The man who has accepted it has certified that God is truthful".
That is all.
The one who accepts this testimony among you will say God is truthful.
John 3:34, "For the one whom God has sent, speaks the Word of God".
The one that God has sent, speaks the Word of truth - the Word of God;
the Word of Spirit - the Word of God.
John 3:34, "for God gives me the Spirit without limit".
Have you listened to that?
The Father gave the Spirit to us to make us like His Son.
John 3:35, "The Father loves the Son and has placed everything in His hands.
Whoever believes in the Son has eternal life".
Whoever believes in the Son has eternal life.
John 3:36, "but whoever rejects the Son will not see life, for God's wrath remains on him".
John 4:1, "The Pharisees heard that Jesus was gaining and baptising
more disciples than John -
although in fact it was not Jesus who baptised, but his disciples".
John 4:3, "When the Lord learnt of this, he left Judea and went back once more to Galilee".
John 4:4, "Now he had to go through Samaria.
John 4:5, "So he came to a town in Samaria called Sychar,
near the plot of ground Jacob had given to his son Joseph".
John 4:6, "Jacob's well was there, and Jesus, tired as he was from the journey,
sat down by the well. It was about the sixth hour".
John 4:7, "When a Samaritan woman came to draw water, Jesus said to her,
'Will you give me a drink?'"
John 4:8, "(His disciples had gone into the town to buy food.)"
John 4:9, "The Samaritan woman said to him, 'You are a Jew and I am a Samaritan woman.
How can you ask me for a drink?' (For Jews do not associate with Samaritans.)"
John 4:10, "Jesus answered her, 'If you knew the gift of God
and who it is that asks you for a drink, you would have asked him
and he would have given you living water'."
Thank you.
Let's hear from the sister.
In fact, I was a 'ghost' talking to you last week Sunday.
But I can tell you that I am a human being now.
All glory to God.
I thank Him so much for giving me a second chance to live.
Rebecca
(Prayer Line Testimony)
What is your message to the youth?
All I can tell the youth is that they should put their hope in God
because He is the only one who can save them.
So, they should trust and believe in God.
You said you have been to many places and we know that you have spent a fortune.
Isn't it?
A lot of money but I now know God.
I know that God is here.
How much have you spent for God to give you so much to restore your life?
Nothing - not a dime.
Rebecca
(Prayer Line Testimony)
Thank you.
Let me thank the sister that brought this sister here.
She spent her money, preached the Gospel, told her that God is the Healer.
I think that God is the rewarder.
Let us just hear a word - what inspired you.
My name is Ms Julia Kujah.
I am the one who brought Rebecca here last week.
My joy knows no bounds.
It was not easy taking on such a challenge
when everyone else was giving up.
But I needed to amass faith because from the onset, we didn't have it easy.
Trying to get her a passport, aside from the usual ups and downs,
the day they asked her to come and collect her passport,
every passport that was printed came out but her own one came out blank.
So I said, "Wow, God, what a challenge!"
But I didn't give up.
Then, the day we were supposed to come, I called her and talked to her.
Then, that evening, I ended up in hospital.
I was admitted; the following day, my son was admitted; we cancelled it.
So, it wasn't an easy thing.
But I thank God that the more the challenges, the more resolved I was.
I brought her here with all the faith I had.
God did not disappoint me.
Indeed, God has done it for her; she is free.
I have talked to her and seen that her confidence has increased.
She is smiling, she can walk straight, she is sleeping.
I've talked to her and asked her if she feels any pain.
She replied, "No pain at all".
She is healed and hearty.
What else can I say but 'Thank You, Jesus'?
Indeed, our faith in Jesus is never in vain.
Those who put their trust in God will never be put to shame.
Rebecca is a testimony, and I want the whole world to know
that they should put their trust in God.
God will never fail you.
If men fail you, turn their backs and give up,
know that God is alive and He will do it.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
I want to give you faith bracelets -
that is just my promise to give to the sister and you.
When you go back to your country, you will go with a shining light.
Rebecca & Family
(Prayer Line Testimony)
Thank you; thank you very much.
My name is Dr Carol Asante.
I work with the Korle-Bu Teaching Hospital.
I am a specialist with the Department of Anaesthesia.
After she came from the Prayer Line, I examined her abdomen
and I found multiple scars on her abdomen which were medical scars.
She didn't have any pain when I palpated her abdomen.
She reported that she had had pain prior to that.
It is the first time that I am giving people publicly.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Giving Out Faith Bracelet
Thank you, Man of God.
Recipients of Faith Bracelet
Thank You, Jesus; thank you, Man of God.
Thank you so very much.
The name 'Emmanuel TV' - all the prayer that we transmit to the whole world,
you are included.
Because as you are going, I know they will try but you have to catch them for me.
They will try you again and then you will catch them for me.
I want them to come to you and confess, "I'm sorry.
I'm the one who sent the pins to your body".
Recipients of Faith Bracelet
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work
in our generation today and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies,
deliverances, sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.
RV: Mel Flowers 17/03/2019